Guide to the Duke Real Estate Office records, 1893-2018 and undated UA.10.04.0007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Real Estate Deeds, 1893-2018; undated
  - File No.: 831, Grantee: E. Judson Pickett, Grantor: Bennett, Type: Deed, 1964 January 20 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 298, Page: 644, Comments/Location: Sumter (Ferrell Lane)
  - File No.: 832, Grantee: E. Judson Pickett, Grantor: Wachovia Bank/L.C. Morton, Type: Deed, 1964 January 13 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 298, Page: 543, Comments/Location: 1012, 1014, 1016 Maxwell
  - File No.: 833, Grantee: E. Judson Pickett, Grantor: P. William Bennett, Type: Deed, 1964 January 6 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 298, Page: 385, Comments/Location: 1017 Maxwell
  - File No.: 834, Grantee: E. Judson Pickett, Grantor: Emma Gibson, Type: Deed, 1964 January 14 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 298, Page: 647, Comments/Location: Maxwell Avenue
  - File No.: 835, Grantee: E. Judson Pickett, Grantor: Lavelle McNeil, Type: Deed, 1964 January 8 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 298, Page: 416, Comments/Location: 1013 Maxwell
  - File No.: 836, Grantee: E. Judson Pickett, Grantor: C.C. Edwards, Type: Deed, 1964 January 7 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 298, Page: 386, Comments/Location: Ames Place
  - File No.: 837, Grantee: E. Judson Pickett, Grantor: Fred Herndon, Type: Deed, 1964 January 13 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 298, Page: 542, Comments/Location: 1018 Maxwell
  - File No.: 838, Grantee: Cletis Pride, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1964 February 28 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #D-6, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 5/Paid in full
  - File No.: 840, Grantee: William H. Durham, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1964 March 31 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #B-4
  - File No.: 841, Grantee: Hugh Robinson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1964 April 14 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #A-2, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 5
  - File No.: 842, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E. Judson Pickett, Type: Deed, 1964 May 6 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Gattis & Maxwell Streets
  - File No.: 843, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E. Judson Pickett, Type: Deed, 1964 May 8 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 302, Page: 1, Comments/Location: Maxwell Avenue
  - File No.: 844, Grantee: Charles Jordan, Sr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1964 June 30 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 845, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Herbert Hahn, Type: Deed, 1965 June 7 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 846, Grantee: Herbert Herring, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1964 July 28 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #D-25
  - File No.: 847, Grantee: Eugene Day, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1964 July 21 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 849, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Mary D. Biddle et al, Type: QC/Deed, 1939 September 7 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 1-3, Comments/Location: Sarah P. Duke Estates/Ch-Hill & Duke St.
  - File No.: 850, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: A. Leslie Wilson, Type: Deed, 1965 March 31 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 851, Grantee: Henry Satterfield, Grantor: CCB, SS&L, Type: Rlse/Deed, 1964 November 25 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Pettigrew, Powe, Old/New File No.: 3022
  - File No.: 852, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Robert B. and Joan I. Clayton, 1964 December 4 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Lot No. F-3
  - File No.: 853, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dr. Deryl Hart & Mary Hart, Type: Deed, 1964 December 21 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 307, Page: 620, Comments/Location: Thaxton Avenue
  - File No.: 854, Grantee: Robert Wheat, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 June 2 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #J-5
  - File No.: 858, Grantee: Robert Wheat, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 June 2 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 860.1, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: A. D. Hamlett, Type: Deed, 1968 January 19 (Box 14)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Dodson Crossroads
  - File No.: 860.2, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E. Judson Pickett, Type: Deed, 1965 May 4 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Dodson Crossroads
  - File No.: 860, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Clarence Wilkins, Type: Deed, 1965 May 24 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 222 and 302 Alexander Ave.
  - File No.: 861, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Donald Stone, Type: DOT/Note, 1965 May 25 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 862, Grantee: Jacinto J. Zazquez, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 May 25 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #J-9
  - File No.: 863, Grantee: W. Scott Gehman, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 May 25 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-11
  - File No.: 864, Grantee: Bruce Wells, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 May 25 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-13
  - File No.: 865, Grantee: John Livesay, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 February 19 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 866, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: E. T. Thompson, Type: Deed, 1965 July 22 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 313, Page: 141, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #9, Comments/Location: Faber and Swift Streets
  - File No.: 867, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Henry Subleth, Jr., Type: DOT/Note, 1967 February 28 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 868, Grantee: Thomas Naylor, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1966 February 23 (Box 14)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-16
  - File No.: 869, Grantee: Paul Hochstein, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 May 26 (Box 14)
  - File No.: 871, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Lloyd Borstelmann, Type: Deed, 1967 August 30 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 872, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Stanley Needel, Type: Deed, 1966 January 7 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-14
  - File No.: 873, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Samson Gross, Type: Deed, 1969 August 1 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 874, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Bronislas Jezierski, Type: Deed, 1966 September 29 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 875, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: William Wallace, Type: Deed, 1966 June 28 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-4
  - File No.: 876, Grantee: Kenneth Hall, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 May 26 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-11, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 877, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Irving Alexander, Type: Deed, 1967 January 16 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #J-3
  - File No.: 878, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Robert Ballentyne, Type: Deed, 1966 June 27 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #J-4
  - File No.: 879, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: M. Paul Capp, Type: Deed, 1968 January 24 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-9
  - File No.: 880, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Furman Barton, Type: Deed, 1967 March 3 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-11
  - File No.: 881, Grantee: Carl Eisdorfer, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1967 October 3 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 882, Grantee: John Fein, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1966 July 1 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 883, Grantee: Thomas Keller, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 May 26 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #J-6
  - File No.: 884, Grantee: Kenneth Knoerr, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 June 2 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-12, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 885, Grantee: Harold Lewis, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 June 1 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-15, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 886, Grantee: Harry Partin, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 June 1 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-18, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 887, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Larry Thompson, Type: Deed, 1967 December 7 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 338, Page: 450, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-12, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6
  - File No.: 888, Grantee: Richard Walter, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 June 3 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-13, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 889, Grantee: William Anlyan, Grantor: Duke University, Type: Deed, 1965 January 25 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 308, Page: 468, Map-Block-Lot: 1517 Pinecrest, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites
  - File No.: 890, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Herbert Massey, Type: Deed, 1965 June 14 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 312, Page: 383, Comments/Location: Onslow Street
  - File No.: 891, Grantee: Richard Lester, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 May 25 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 892, Grantee: Dwight M. Smith, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 June 8 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-2
  - File No.: 895, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Henry Helmers, Type: Deed, 1968 November 11 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 896, Grantee: H. Trevar Williams, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 May 26 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-8, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 897, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Aleksandar Vesic, Type: Deed, 1969 January 9 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-18
  - File No.: 898, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Gerrie Kilburn, Type: Deed, 1966 September 7 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-13
  - File No.: 899, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Central Engineering, Type: Deed, 1965 March 1 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 312, Page: 566, Map-Block-Lot: Map 475-3-1, Comments/Location: Teer House Property, Roxboro Road
  - File No.: 900, Grantee: William Van Alstyne, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 July 9 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-13
  - File No.: 901, Grantee: Robert Klein, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 July 14 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 902, Grantee: Thomas Gallie, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1967 April 12 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #J1-A
  - File No.: 903, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Frederick McFalls, Type: Deed, 1967 July 25 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 904, Grantee: Raymond Massengill, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 July 20 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 905, Grantee: Jacob Burlak, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 August 16 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #J-2, Comments/Location: SEC. 6/Sold to L. Anderson/Paid in full
  - File No.: 906, Grantee: Joseph Wadsworth, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1965 August 31 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #4, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 5/Paid in full
  - File No.: 907, Grantee: David Sabiston, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1967 June 26 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #5, Comments/Location: 1528 Pinecrest Road/Paid in full
  - File No.: 909, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Robert Spaulding, Type: Deed, 1967 March 8 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-10, Comments/Location: Duke Homesite, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 910, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Herbert Crovitz, Type: DOT/Note, 1966 August 26 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 911, Grantee: E. W. Dunham, Grantor: Duke, Type: Rlse/Deed, 1965 September 13 (Box 15)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: E. Cot Mills Deed 10-2-45/Use of roadway
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Burlington Industries, Type: DOT, 1965 November 1 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 316, Page: 271, Comments/Location: 16 Tracts of Land
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: K. P. Lewis, Type: Deed, 1907 July 26 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 37, Page: 337, Comments/Location: Blacknall & Lake Avenue
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: W. A. Erwin, Type: Deed, 1895 April 12 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Minnie Christian, Type: Deed, 1919 November 4 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: George Harris, Type: Deed, 1922 April 24 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Baptist Council of Durham, Type: Deed, 1953 June 2 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Durham RE & Ins, Type: Deed, 1961 August 24 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Durham RE & Ins, Type: Deed, 1961 October 17 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 279, Page: 542, Comments/Location: Blacknall Street
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: T. J. Rigsbee, Type: Deed, 2009 April 15 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Drury Mayes, Type: Deed, 2009 March 8 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: T. J. Rigsbee, Type: QC/Deed, 2016 September 15 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Durham Loan & Trust, Type: Deed, 2009 March 25 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Joseph Whitfield, Type: Deed, 2015 June 22 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: A. L. Bowen, Type: Deed, 2015 March 4 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: W. L. Foushee, Type: Deed, 2018 October 10 (Box 15)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2043.
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: S. C. Gooch, Type: Deed, 1932 August 12 (Box 15)
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: W. D. Coble, Type: Deed, 1933 May 1 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 107, Page: 309, Comments/Location: Bailey Street
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: F.L. Fuller, Jr. Trustee, Type: Deed, 1933 August 16 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 109, Page: 153, Comments/Location: 310 & 401 Oregon Street
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Ludlow Rogers, Comm., Type: Deed, 1933 August 3 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 109, Page: 135, Comments/Location: Bynum Street
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Citizens Investment, Type: Deed, 1933 December 1 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 76, Page: 696, Comments/Location: Oregon Street
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: W. C. Purcell, Type: Deed, 1934 March 7 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 112, Page: 27, Comments/Location: Bynum Street
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: A. H. McDonald, Type: Deed, 1934 March 14 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 110, Page: 206, Comments/Location: Bynum Street
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: H. W. Webb, Comm., Type: Deed, 1934 September 13 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 113, Page: 112, Comments/Location: Jones Street
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Jones, Graham/Durham RE&I, Type: Deed, 1963 January 4 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 289, Page: 695, Comments/Location: Yearby & Alexander
  - File No.: 913, Grantee: Erwin Cotton Mills, Grantor: Durham RE & Ins, Type: Deed, 1962 January 4 (Box 15)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 289, Page: 700, Comments/Location: 211 Alexander Avenue
  - File No.: 914, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Everett Harold Hopkins, Type: Deed, 1966 January 10 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 53, Page: 26
  - File No.: 915, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dailey Property, Type: Deed, 1965 December 27 (Box 16)
    County: Alamance, Deed Book: 333, Page: 267, Comments/Location: Alamance County
  - File No.: 916, Grantee: Jane Philpot, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1966 February 20 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 917, Grantee: Craufurd Goodwin, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1977 August 12 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 918, Grantee: Robert E. Cushman, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1966 January 20 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-14, Comments/Location: Homesites,Sec. 6/Sold to Cully Carson
  - File No.: 919, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Mary G. Carter, Type: Deed, 1966 February 1 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 318, Page: 687, Comments/Location: Swift & Page
  - File No.: 920, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Greystone Trustees, Type: QC/Deed, 1966 February 4 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: From Erwin Mills, 220 Alexander Ave.
  - File No.: 921, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Townhouse Apartments, Inc., Type: Deed, 1966 March 31 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 320, Page: 360, Comments/Location: Townhouse Apts., Swift Avenue
  - File No.: 922, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Wachovia - Eliz. Davenport, Type: Deed, 1966 April 5 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Cent. Camp. Hous., Yearby Ave. (1915-17)
  - File No.: 923, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Cheek Property, Type: Deed, 1966 May 31 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1911 Yearby
  - File No.: 924, Grantee: Theo C. Pilkington, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1967 May 31 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 927, Grantee: Cliff Wing, Grantor: Duke, Type: DOT, 1966 August 18 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 932, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Joe Colton, Type: Deed, 1968 September 9 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 347, Page: 87, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-12, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 6/Sold to P. Carrington
  - File No.: 933, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Viola Houston, Type: Deed, 1966 October 5 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 807-809 Onslow Street
  - File No.: 934, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thomas D. Wright, Type: Deed, 1966 September 28 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #15-16, Comments/Location: Wilkerson Avenue
  - File No.: 936, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Minnie Thompson, Type: Deed, 1966 October 28 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1016-1016 1/2 -1018 1/2 Wilkerson Ave.
  - File No.: 938, Grantee: John Jimenez, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1967 March 3 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #F-10
  - File No.: 939, Grantee: Herbert Hacker, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1967 March 13 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-16, Comments/Location: Duke Homesite, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 940, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Chapel Towers, Type: Deed, 1966 December 28 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 410-412 Anderson; 2003-2009 Yearby
  - File No.: 941, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Eddie Brandon, Type: Deed, 1967 May 4 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 806 Onslow
  - File No.: 943, Grantee: John E. Staddon, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1976 April 26 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots A-8&9, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 5/Paid in full
  - File No.: 944, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Elijah Menefee, Type: Deed, 1968 October 11 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 945, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Duke Power, Type: Rlse/Deed, 1966 December 28 (Box 16)
    County: Chatham, Conveyed by File No.: 945.1, Comments/Location: 34 tracts of land, Haw River Division, Duke Forest
  - File No.: 945.1, Grantee: State of North Carolina, Grantor: Duke University, Type: Deed, 2003 December 19 (Box 16)
    Deeds in the Real Estate Office are copies of public records, and are open for research. Additional materials under administrative restriction until 2028.
    County: Chatham, Deed Book: 1076, Page: 109, Comments/Location: 1,214 acres, Haw River Division Duke Forest, Old/New File No.: 56.7
  - File No.: 946, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: William Katzenmeyer, Type: Deed, 1972 January 28 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #4, Comments/Location: Homesites, Sec. 8/SOLD TO R. WALTER, Old/New File No.: 320.3
  - File No.: 947, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Betty R. and Edna Garrard, Type: Deed, 1967 July 28 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 1913 Yearby Street, Old/New File No.: 447.2
  - File No.: 948, Grantee: John A. Fowler, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1969 March 19 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-15, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full, Old/New File No.: 123.9
  - File No.: 949, Grantee: I.S. Johnsrude, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1967 August 24 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 810, Page: 598, Comments/Location: 2702 Spencer St./Paid in full/HOMESITE
  - File No.: 950, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: R. O. Everette, Type: Deed, 1967 August 25 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Maplewood Ave. (Rear of 1020 Burch)
  - File No.: 951, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Madge Nicholson, Type: Deed, 1967 August 30 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 813 Onslow Street, Old/New File No.: 948.1
  - File No.: 952, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: State of North Carolina, Type: ROW, 1967 August 31 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Right of Way Agreement
  - File No.: 953, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Elizabeth Councilman, Type: Deed, 1967 September 7 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 313 Garden Street
  - File No.: 954, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Harold Lebovitz, Type: Deed, 1968 April 26 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 343, Page: 44, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-15, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 6/Paid in full
  - File No.: 955, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Wayland Hedgepeth, Type: Deed, 1978 February 21 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 956, Grantee: David Yandle, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1967 October 12 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #D-7, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 5/Paid in full
  - File No.: 958, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: NCNB, 1967 September 22 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Agreement/821 Onslow Street
  - File No.: 963.1 (963.A), Grantee: NCNB, Grantor: Duke, 1967 September 29 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Agreement/various property
  - File No.: 963, Grantee: NCNB, Grantor: Duke, 1967 September 13 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Mgmt Termination K (Buchanan, Green, Markham, Onslow)
  - File No.: 964, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Ada G. Cheek, Type: Deed, 1967 November 16 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Yearby Street
  - File No.: 965, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Louis D. Volpp, Type: Deed, 1968 October 29 (Box 16)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 348, Page: 391, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #E-12, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec 6
  - File No.: 966, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Bruce Crumpacker, Type: Deed, 1967 November 27 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 967, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: NCNB, Type: Deed, 1967 August 31 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 969, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Richard D. Hobbet, Type: DOT/Note, 1969 January 24 (Box 16)
  - File No.: 970, Grantee: Roberts Construction Co., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 January 15 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 7.4 acres - Chapel Hill Blvd.
  - File No.: 972, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: W. W. Elliott, Type: Deed, 1970 January 6 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 973, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. Horst M. Meyer, Type: DOT/Note, 1968 September 19 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 975, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Larry Thompson, Type: Deed, 1974 September 6 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 976, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: William Willis, Type: Deed, 1969 December 17 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 977, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Merrell/Cynthia Patrick, Type: DOT/Note, 1969 March 18 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 979, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: C.R. & Hilda Matheson, Type: Deed, 1968 March 27 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 980, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Chrls/Don/Sarah Christian, Type: Deed, 1969 January 20 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 984, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Paul & Zeren Earls, Type: Deed, 1971 July 27 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 379, Page: 66, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #27, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 985, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Milton & Frida Raben, Type: Deed, 1968 March 19 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 986, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Vladimir & Emma Treml, Type: Deed, 1969 April 9 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 987, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Robert & Jane Whalen, Type: Deed, 1969 May 23 (Box 17)
  - File No.: 988, Grantee: Benjamin & Nancy Trump, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1968 February 8 (Box 17)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #37, Comments/Location: Duke Homesites, Sec. 7/Paid in full
  - File No.: 989, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Melvin & Carol Braaten, Type: Deed, 1969 January 7 (Box 17)